(Penny:)Smush, smush, smush.
- You're hurting me.
- No, Sheldon hurt you.
- Before. Now it's you.
- Oh.
l think I understand.
(Sheldon:)You're the one person who can say
Sheldon Cooper is your boyfriend.
(Sheldon:)But that rings hollow if you can't
lord him over others in the flesh.
l forget what I bring to the party
and what I take away when I leave.
(Sheldon:)Please accept these valuable
Cooper Coupons...
(Sheldon:)- ...as restitution.
- She doesn't want your stupid coupons...
The Science Center? Redeeming. Let's go.
(Sheldon:)Well played, Amy Farrah Fowler.
Let me get my coat.
(Sheldon:)Oh, grow up, Leonard.
(Raj:)Excuse me, I have something to say.
(Raj:)None of you may realize it, but I was very
much looking forward to this weekend.